Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.3.6
Marist College
  Box 1537
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Adirondacks [photograph of Lowell Thomas], circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1537)
    - [Lowell Thomas in Hat] [3 copies], 1
  - Subject files: Admirals Banquet, 1950; 6 (Box 1537)
    - Admirals Banquet - Del Coronado, San Diego; 1950, 1
    - Verso: Admirals Banquet - Del Coronado, San Diego; 1950, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Advertising Club, circa 1930s - 1940s; 7 (Box 1537)
    - Bernard McFadden [Bernarr MacFadden]; De Seversky; [Alexsander de Seversky] [?]; Paul; Jim Doolittle, 1
    - Verso: Bernard McFadden [Bernarr MacFadden]; De Seversky; [Alexsander de Seversky] [?]; Paul; Jim Doolittle, 1-verso
    - H.G.T. [Harry G. Thomas, immediately behind Lowell Thomas] - Sam Pryor - Jacques Charmoz, Paul Lockwood (center rear), 2
    - Verso: H.G.T. [Harry G. Thomas, immediately behind Lowell Thomas] - Sam Pryor - Jacques Charmoz, Paul Lockwood (center rear), 2-verso
    - Alex Forbes, 3
    - Verso: Alex Forbes, 3-verso
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at right in rear], 4
    - [Gene] Sarazen - Colliers, 5
    - Verso: [Gene] Sarazen - Colliers, 5-verso
    - Kent Cooper, Fr. Gannett, Roy Howard, Sen. Curly Brooks, Paul Block, A. Sulzberger N.Y. Times, Jas. Stahlman, Julius Ochs Adler N.Y. Times -Gen. Mgr., Hugh Baillie, Frank B. Noyes Wash. Star, Gil T. Hodges Pub. N.Y. Sun., [?] head of B.P., 6
    - Verso: Kent Cooper, Fr. Gannett, Roy Howard, Sen. Curly Brooks, Paul Block, A. Sulzberger N.Y. Times, Jas. Stahlman, Julius Ochs Adler N.Y. Times -Gen. Mgr., Hugh Baillie, Frank B. Noyes Wash. Star, Gil T. Hodges Pub. N.Y. Sun., [?] head of B.P., 6-verso
    - Warden Lawes, Homer Croy, Chase Taylor, Paul Webb, Eddie Eagen, Ted Shane, Mike Fiaschetti, Truman Talley-Police Comm?, 7
    - Verso: Warden Lawes, Homer Croy, Chase Taylor, Paul Webb, Eddie Eagen, Ted Shane, Mike Fiaschetti, Truman Talley-Police Comm?, 7-verso
    - Dudley Field Malone, [?] Warwick, 8
    - Verso: Dudley Field Malone, [?] Warwick, 8-verso
    - Bernard McFadden [Bernarr MacFadden], Homer Rodeheaver, Dr. Wm. Montgomery McGovern, Lynn Sumner, 9
    - Verso: Bernard McFadden [Bernarr MacFadden], Homer Rodeheaver, Dr. Wm. Montgomery McGovern, Lynn Sumner, 9-verso
    - Upton Close, Gabriel Heater, Geo. Sokolsky, Johannes Steel, Berton Brayley [Braley?], Don Herold, 10
    - Verso: Upton Close, Gabriel Heater, Geo. Sokolsky, Johannes Steel, Berton Brayley [Braley?], Don Herold, 10-verso
    - Caesar Sershinger (glasses), A. Barkley, A. Woolcott, Farley, Gen. Ted "T.R." [Theodore Roosevelt, Jr.], Freddie D. Benham, 11
    - Verso: Caesar Sershinger (glasses), A. Barkley, A. Woolcott, Farley, Gen. Ted "T.R." [Theodore Roosevelt, Jr.], Freddie D. Benham, 11-verso
    - Rube Goldberg - John Kieran, P. Waxman, Croy, Shane, Saucier, Chase Taylor, Berton Braley, 12
    - Verso: Rube Goldberg - John Kieran, P. Waxman, Croy, Shane, Saucier, Chase Taylor, Berton Braley, 12-verso
    - Bruce Burton is standing directly behind the small boy??.., 13
    - Verso: Bruce Burton is standing directly behind the small boy??.., 13-verso
    - [Vilhjalmur Stefansson, Lowell Thomas, others], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Advertising Club], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas presenting a plaque at the Advertising Club of New York], 16
    - [Advertising Club of New York caricatures], 17
  - Subject files: Airlines, circa 1950s; 8 (Box 1537)
    - Photo taken of Mr. Lowell Thomas, famous radio commentator of the United States, deplaning at Tocumen Airport, in Panama, from Panagra flight 320. 25 August 1951, 1
    - Verso: Photo taken of Mr. Lowell Thomas, famous radio commentator of the United States, deplaning at Tocumen Airport, in Panama, from Panagra flight 320. 25 August 1951, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas tipping his hat while boaring a plane], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of "Northeast" plane], 3
  - Subject files: Airplane crash [Lowell Thomas], circa 1926; 9 (Box 1537)
    - Note: This is a precious picture. It is the only one LT has of the plane in which he crashed years ago in Andalusia?, 1
    - Plane that crashed in Andalusia? [5 copies], 2
    - Plane that crashed in Andalusia? [3 copies], 3
  - Subject files: Airplanes, circa 1920s; 10 (Box 1537)
    - Spad; Magasin Moderne de Photogaphie; Charles Meyer, 21, Rue des Pyramides, 21, Paris, 1
    - Verso: Spad; Magasin Moderne de Photogaphie; Charles Meyer, 21, Rue des Pyramides, 21, Paris, 1-verso
    - Nieuport; Magasin Moderne de Photogaphie; Charles Meyer, 21, Rue des Pyramides, 21, Paris, 2
    - Verso: Nieuport; Magasin Moderne de Photogaphie; Charles Meyer, 21, Rue des Pyramides, 21, Paris, 2-verso
    - [Bi-plane], 3
  - Subject files: Alaska Airlines (Russia) [color photographs], 1970; 11 (Box 1537)
    - Note: Russia 1970; Inaugural flight, Alaska Airlines, 1
    - [Lowell Thomas in Russia], 2
    - [Man and woman with a coffee dispenser (?) in Russia], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others in front of a plane], 4
  - Subject files: Amazon River landscape photographs by Captain A. W. Stevens, United States Army Air Corps, circa 1920s - 1930s; 12 (Box 1537)
    - 80 foot waterfall, Rio Uraricoera - 1096, 1
    - Verso: 80 foot waterfall, Rio Uraricoera - 1096, 1-verso
    - Amazon trees covered with parasitic growth - 196, 2
    - Verso: Amazon trees covered with parasitic growth - 196, 2-verso
    - The flat Amazon country, with first foothills in distance - 1125, 3
    - Verso: The flat Amazon country, with first foothills in distance - 1125, 3-verso
    - Amazon River - 389, 4
    - Verso: Amazon River - 389, 4-verso
    - Rio Branco and Sierra Grande - Amazonas - 475, 5
    - Verso: Rio Branco and Sierra Grande - Amazonas - 475, 5-verso
    - Settlement - Rio Branco - 762, 6
    - Verso: Settlement - Rio Branco - 762, 6-verso
    - Bank of Amazon River - 398, 7
    - Verso: Bank of Amazon River - 398, 7-verso
    - Boa Vista - Rio Branco - 466, 8
    - Verso: Boa Vista - Rio Branco - 466, 8-verso
    - Indian hut and Mandioca clearing - Amazonas - T-29, 9
    - Verso: Indian hut and Mandioca clearing - Amazonas - T-29, 9-verso
    - Rapids - (Caxioera) Rio Uraricoera - A tributary of the Rio Branco, emptying with Rio Negro into Amazon - 504, 10
    - Verso: Rapids - (Caxioera) Rio Uraricoera - A tributary of the Rio Branco, emptying with Rio Negro into Amazon - 504, 10-verso
    - Rapids - Rio Uraricoera tributary of Rio Branco - 514, 11
    - Verso: Rapids - Rio Uraricoera tributary of Rio Branco - 514, 11-verso
    - Rapids - Rio Branco, Amazonas - 333, 12
    - Verso: Rapids - Rio Branco, Amazonas - 333, 12-verso
    - Verso: Rio Uraricoera, Amazonas - 503, 13
    - Rio Uraricoera, Amazonas - 503, 13-verso
    - Ceiba tree (question spelling), Amazon - 202, 14
    - Verso: Ceiba tree (question spelling), Amazon - 202, 14-verso
    - Large forest tree - Amazon River - 667, 15
    - Verso: Large forest tree - Amazon River - 667, 15-verso
    - Manaos [Manaus], Brazil - 344, 16
    - Verso: Manaos [Manaus], Brazil - 344, 16-verso
    - Manaos [Manaus], Brazil - 346, 17
    - Verso: Manaos [Manaus], Brazil - 346, 17-verso
    - Manaos [Manaus], Brazil - 355, 18
    - Verso: Manaos [Manaus], Brazil - 355, 18-verso
  - Subject files: American Academy of Achievement [color photographs], 1971; 13 (Box 1537)
    - [Lowell Thomas giving a speech], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas giving a speech at the American Academy of Achievement], 2
    - Note: [letter from Northwestern Mutual Life] Dear Mr. Thomas, Your activity must require your attendance at so many of these affairs that perhaps you connot even keep track of them. During the course of the American Academy of Achievement Meeting, time was so short that I had no opportunity for personal visit with you but I did think that these snaps that I got were good enough so that you might like to have them for your collection. Please accept them with my compliments. Sincerely, [signed] John O. Todd, 3
  - Subject files: Amos 'N' Andy, circa 1928 - 1959; 14 (Box 1537)
    - Amos 'N' Andy, 1
    - Verso: Amos + Andy, 1-verso
    - Note: AMOS 'N' ANDY - 20 YEARS AGO: But in 1928 when Freeman (Amos) Gosden and Charles (Andy) Correll first went on the air as a team, on Chicago's WMAQ, they were known as Sam 'N' Henry. A year later, they changed their names to Amos 'N' Andy, became a network show and an immediate national hit. Theirs was the first nightly continual broadcast - 12/28/48, 2
    - Amos + Andy and LT - extra copy; Apr. 1959, 3
    - Verso: Amos + Andy and LT - extra copy; Apr. 1959, 3-verso
    - LT flanked by "Amos and Andy"; with Amos + Andy; also 30 years later, 4
    - Verso: LT flanked by "Amos and Andy"; with Amos + Andy; also 30 years later, 4-verso
    - ["Amos and Andy" radio show (?)], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas radio broadcast on NBC], 6
  - Subject files: Antarctica, 1956 December - 1962 January; 15 (Box 1537)
    - USN 808874, 12-31-1956 Part of Adelie penguin rookery at Cape Hallett, which has estimated population of 150,000; Official US Navy photograph by Dietrich, Joi; Released; U.S. Naval Photographic Center; U.S Naval Station, Anacostia; Washington 25, D.C., 1
    - Verso: USN 808874, 12-31-1956 Part of Adelie penguin rookery at Cape Hallett, which has estimated population of 150,000; Official US Navy photograph by Dietrich, Joi; Released; U.S. Naval Photographic Center; U.S Naval Station, Anacostia; Washington 25, D.C., 1-verso
    - Subject - Two scientists from the United Kingdom's Halley Bay Station on the Eastern coast of Antarctica explore the ice cliffs along the coast. Extreme winds, often reaching 100 MPH, and blowing snow carves natural sculptures into the thick ice mountains. Antarctica is the highest of thw World's seven continents with an average elevation of about 7,500 feet. It's also the coldest and windiest of the continents. The Soviet Union's Vostok Station recorded the world's coldest temperature of 126.9 degrees below zero Fahrenheit on August 24, 1960, 2
    - Verso: Subject - Two scientists from the United Kingdom's Halley Bay Station on the Eastern coast of Antarctica explore the ice cliffs along the coast. Extreme winds, often reaching 100 MPH, and blowing snow carves natural sculptures into the thick ice mountains. Antarctica is the highest of thw World's seven continents with an average elevation of about 7,500 feet. It's also the coldest and windiest of the continents. The Soviet Union's Vostok Station recorded the world's coldest temperature of 126.9 degrees below zero Fahrenheit on August 24, 1960, 2-verso
    - XAM-0450(L)-10-61; VX NAF MCMURDO, 25 October 1961; Kazukaitis F. PHC; Emperor penguins and chicks at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Emperor penguins are one of the largest birds, weighing close to ninety pounds and standing three feet tall; the emperor lays and hatches its single egg on the ice during the long Antarctic winter night. Eggs are incubated in a snug corner [?], 3
    - Verso XAM-0450(L)-10-61; VX NAF MCMURDO, 25 October 1961; Kazukaitis F. PHC; Emperor penguins and chicks at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Emperor penguins are one of the largest birds, weighing close to ninety pounds and standing three feet tall; the emperor lays and hatches its single egg on the ice during the long Antarctic winter night. Eggs are incubated in a snug corner [?], 3-verso
    - Task Force Forty Three, XAM 0449(L)-10-61; 25 October 1961; Emperor penguin and chick at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. The Emperor penguin is one of the largest birds, weighing close to ninety pounds and standing three feet tall. The Emperor lays and hatches its single egg on the ice during the long Antarctic winter night. Eggs are incubated in a snug corner between the tops of the penguin's feet and the rolls of fat on their lower abdomen?. Credit line should read, "Official U.S. Navy Photograph," by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC F. Kazukaitis, USN), 4
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAM 0449(L)-10-61; 25 October 1961; Emperor penguin and chick at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. The Emperor penguin is one of the largest birds, weighing close to ninety pounds and standing three feet tall. The Emperor lays and hatches its single egg on the ice during the long Antarctic winter night. Eggs are incubated in a snug corner between the tops of the penguin's feet and the rolls of fat on their lower abdomen?. Credit line should read, "Official U.S. Navy Photograph," by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC F. Kazukaitis, USN), 4-verso
    - Task Force Forty Three, XAM 2301(L)-1-62; 10 January 1962; Concerned mother penguin sits on her chick and an incubating egg at the same time in the midst of a crowded rookery at Inexpressible Island, 200 miles north of McMurdo Station, Antarctica. These penguins, of the Adelie variety, hatch and raise their young during the relatively mild Antarctic summer. Credit line to read, "Official U.S. Navy Photograph ," by Photographer's Mate Airman (PHAN) Mark W. Huntley, USN, 5
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAM 2301(L)-1-62; 10 January 1962; Concerned mother penguin sits on her chick and an incubating egg at the same time in the midst of a crowded rookery at Inexpressible Island, 200 miles north of McMurdo Station, Antarctica. These penguins, of the Adelie variety, hatch and raise their young during the relatively mild Antarctic summer. Credit line to read, "Official U.S. Navy Photograph ," by Photographer's Mate Airman (PHAN) Mark W. Huntley, USN, 5-verso
  - Subject files: Antarctica [includes color photographs], 1962 November - December; 16 (Box 1537)
    - 18 November 1962; The Honorable Luther H. Hodges, Secretary of Commerce, (left) and Lowell Thomas, internationally known commentator, prior to the Secretary's news conference at Harewood International Airport, Christchurch, New Zealand., 1
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30026-11-62; 18 November 1962; The Honorable Luther H. Hodges, Secretary of Commerce, (left) and Lowell Thomas, internationally known commentator, prior to the Secretary's news conference at Harewood International Airport, Christchurch, New Zealand. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate First Class (PH1) Marco Billante, USN, 1-verso
    - 20 November 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Honorable Luther H. Hodges, RADM [Rear Admiral] David M. Tyree, USN, Commander Naval Support Force, Antarctica, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, wave to the men of McMurdo Station, after their arrival at Williams Field, McMurdo Station, for an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic., 2
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30161-11-62; 20 November 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Honorable Luther H. Hodges, RADM [Rear Admiral] David M. Tyree, USN, Commander Naval Support Force, Antarctica, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, wave to the men of McMurdo Station, after their arrival at Williams Field, McMurdo Station, for an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) Frank Kazukaitis, USN., 2-verso
    - 20 November 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Honorable Luther H. Hodges, RADM [Rear Admiral] David M. Tyree, USN, Commander Naval Support Force, Antarctica, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, wave to the men of McMurdo Station, after their arrival at Williams Field, McMurdo Station, for an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic., 3
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30161-11-62; 20 November 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Honorable Luther H. Hodges, RADM [Rear Admiral] David M. Tyree, USN, Commander Naval Support Force, Antarctica, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, wave to the men of McMurdo Station, after their arrival at Williams Field, McMurdo Station, for an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) Frank Kazukaitis, USN., 3-verso
    - 20 Nov 1962, Visiting dignitaries tour U. S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. Here, Mr. Joe Grossman of the New York Herald Tribune, General James E. Doolittle, ESAF (Ret), Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica, and Mr. Lowell Thomas renown American commentator visit the South Pole., 4
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30115-11-62; 20 Nov 1962, Visiting dignitaries tour U. S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. Here, Mr. Joe Grossman of the New York Herald Tribune, General James E. Doolittle, ESAF (Ret), Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica, and Mr. Lowell Thomas renown American commentator visit the South Pole. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN, 4-verso
    - 20 November 1962; Visiting dignitaries tour U.S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. Congressman C. Hosmer of California (left) and Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator, display a seasonal greeting card at the South Pole., 5
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30100-11-62; 20 November 1962; Visiting dignitaries tour U.S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. Congressman C. Hosmer of California (left) and Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator, display a seasonal greeting card at the South Pole. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN, 5-verso
    - 20 November 1962; Congressman R. Taylor of North Carolina (left) and Mr. Lowell Thomas display seasonal greeting card at the South Pole., 6
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30106-11-62; 20 November 1962; Congressman R. Taylor of North Carolina (left) and Mr. Lowell Thomas display seasonal greeting card at the South Pole. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN., 6-verso
    - [5 copies] 20 Nov 1962, Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator is welcomed to Antarctica by rear Admiral James R. Reedy, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica. Mr. Thomas was among a group which toured U.S. scientific stations in the Antarctic, 7
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30128-11-62; 20 Nov 1962, Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator is welcomed to Antarctica by rear Admiral James R. Reedy, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica. Mr. Thomas was among a group which toured U.S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN., 7-verso
    - 20 Nov 1962, Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander, U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica (center) and U. S. Commerce Secretary the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges at the South Pole., 8
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30112-11-62; 20 Nov 1962, Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander, U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica (center) and U. S. Commerce Secretary the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges at the South Pole. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN, 8-verso
    - [3 copies] 20 Nov 1962, Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander, U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica (center) and U. S. Commerce Secretary the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges at the South Pole., 9
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30112-11-62; 20 Nov 1962, Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander, U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica (center) and U. S. Commerce Secretary the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges at the South Pole. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN, 9-verso
    - [6 copies] 20 Nov 1962; Visiting dignitaries tour U. S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. (L to R) Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, USN, Prospective Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica; Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio commentator; and Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica., 10
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30150-11-62; 20 Nov 1962; Visiting dignitaries tour U. S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. (L to R) Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, USN, Prospective Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica; Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio commentator; and Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN, 10-verso
    - [left to right: Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, USN, Prospective Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica; Lowell Thomas; and Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica], 11
    - 20 Nov 1962; Visiting dignitaries tour New Byrd Station during an inspection trip of U. S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. (L to R) Mr. Larry Martin, scientific leader for New Byrd Station; Mr. Voit Gilmore, director U. S. Travel Service; Mr. Lowell Thomas, American commentator and correspondent; Congressman Holifield of California; and Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, prospective Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica., 12
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30094-11-62; 20 Nov 1962; Visiting dignitaries tour New Byrd Station during an inspection trip of U. S. scientific stations in the Antarctic. (L to R) Mr. Larry Martin, scientific leader for New Byrd Station; Mr. Voit Gilmore, director U. S. Travel Service; Mr. Lowell Thomas, American commentator and correspondent; Congressman Holifield of California; and Rear Admiral James R. Reedy, prospective Commander U. S. Naval Support Force, Antarctica. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) Frank Kazukaitis, USN., 12-verso
    - 20 Nov 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges, presented a pictures donated by the National Geographic Society to personnel of New Byrd Station, Antarctica. (L to R) Gen, James E. Doolittle, USAF (Ret), Secretary Hodges, Dr. James Mooney Deputy Antarctic Projects Officer, and Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator., 13
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30141-1-62; 20 Nov 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges, presented a pictures donated by the National Geographic Society to personnel of New Byrd Station, Antarctica. (L to R) Gen, James E. Doolittle, USAF (Ret), Secretary Hodges, Dr. James Mooney Deputy Antarctic Projects Officer, and Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) Frank Kazukaitis, USN., 13-verso
    - 20 November 1962; A picture donated by the National Geographic Society is carried to New Byrd Station, Antarctica by (L to R) Dr. James Mooney, Deputy Antarctic Projects Officer, Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator, and the U. S. Secretary of Commerce the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges. Secretary Hodges presents the picture at New Byrd Station., 14